My wedding was on a
passing May
day.  The morning began the way
I love
most: quietly and
patiently waiting for the
twilight to
give way to the sun.  And
then I went to choose the
flowers I would use
for my wedding
bouquet.  I have such
nervous excitement,
you know, like butterflies
flying in my stomach.  So,
I'm really looking forward to starting
the ceremony, because
the anticipation of so
many events is
a little scary, but in a
good way.  This is
difficult to explain.  I
made my own
bouquet because I knew it was
very important to me
.  These are comfrey,
arnica, and
balsam root.
These are flowers that have always
brought me
a lot of joy and
lifted my spirits
when I was
outdoors.  So it was
fitting to thank them by
including them in this
special day.  It looks like
I
painted my nails terribly,
but we'll ignore
that and move on.
Now I'm trying on
a dress, taking some
photos among the
wildflowers, and then
I'll meet my family.
I knew it was important for me
to spend
the morning in peace and
reflection, preparing
for the meeting to
begin the holiday.
I send you my
love.  I'm worried,
happy, worried
and happy again.  So,
I hope you have a
great week.
See you soon.
Goodbye.  The day
turned out to be beautiful.
There were light rains and
we saw a rainbow.
Even during
the ceremony, a
small
hummingbird flew to us.  It was
just wonderful.  And I am
so happy that I can
share with you
at least a small
part of our
holiday.